<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Horoscope of the Day</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="chooseText">Choose Your Sign</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <!-- Strings used for horoscopes -->
    <string name="ariesText">You have much more creativity than you think you do, especially today,
        when the universe is sending you a bright can-do attitude. Good thing, too, because you
        could be thrust into a situation that forces you to think on your feet and come up with some
        quick answers. Have no fear and you will have lots of fun. It\'s time to stop worrying about
        what is right or wrong and just do what feels right. Forget about breaking the rules.
        Make your own new ones.
    </string>
    <string name="taurusText">Usually you can be tolerant of just about anything, but today your
        sensitivity level is high and your temper is short. If you want to keep from blowing your
        top, you should do whatever you can to avoid all the people who have pushed you near the
        breaking point in the past. But if you are itching for a fight, these are the people you
        should walk right up to early in the day. Getting everything off your chest might feel
        awfully good and empowering.
    </string>
    <string name="geminiText">People who disagree with you might be annoying and troublesome, but
        they do have a right to their own opinions no matter how wrong they may be! If you can keep
        that attitude in mind today, you will actually enjoy coming across people who don\'t think
        the way you do about some hot topics. You will have an absolute blast debating different
        positions and learning why other people see things the way they do. This kind of
        intellectual conflict stimulates you.
    </string>
    <string name="cancerText">Planned expenses are fine, but acting on impulse at your favorite
        online store is not advised right now. You are going to need more money in the coming weeks,
        and it would be very wise to stay as cash rich as you possibly can. If you need to, get a
        friend to distract you and keep you from buying stuff you don\'t really need. They\'ll help
        you find a way to have fun for free by making cookies, watching TV, or reading a book.
    </string>
    <string name="leoText">Make an effort to talk to that person no one else will talk to, to solve
        that problem that has been plaguing you for so long, to fix that household item once and for
        all, whatever. Trying will take you a long way today, perhaps even all the way to success.
        Even if your heart isn\'t totally into it, you should give it a go anyway. If you always shy
        away from things that make you uncomfortable or intimidate you, you\'ll never go as far as
        you could.</string>
    <string name="virgoText">Be flexible and you will be more powerful. Being too rigid about life
        closes you off to too many things. If you push things away that confuse you or frustrate
        you, you could be depriving yourself of some amazing growth opportunities. It\'s time to
        leave your comfort zone behind and open up your mind and heart. Take a risk and see what
        happens. Roll with the punches and know that no matter what happens, you can totally handle
        it.
    </string>
    <string name="libraText">Hope is the word to hold on to today. No matter how unlikely success
        seems from where you\'re standing now, amazing things can happen. You must think positively
        because you know in your heart that positive things can happen. People can show up from out
        of the blue. Mother Nature can sweep in and change everything. Money can be found in the
        pocket of a coat forgotten in the back of the closet. The answer to your problem is out
        there. Open your mind to it.
    </string>
    <string name="scorpioText">Take things slowly today and give yourself time to be able to focus
        on saying the right things to the right people, especially if you\'re in a delicate
        negotiation with someone. You should watch yourself but be confident, too. Don\'t be afraid
        to push for what you want. Adding a dash of humor to the situation will help you gain some
        ground and keep the tone light and pleasant. You don\'t have to be super serious to get some
        serious stuff done.
    </string>
    <string name="sagittariusText">You can\'t always be as generous as you would like to be with
        your friends. When you don\'t have the time, you don\'t have the time. Trying to convince
        yourself otherwise is only going to make you resent them for forcing you to squeeze your
        already tight schedule even tighter. Don\'t make promises you don\'t feel comfortable
        keeping. They will respect you much more if you say you can\'t help out than if you say you
        can and then just flake out at the last minute.
    </string>
    <string name="capricornText">Your business schedule might be causing problems with your social
        schedule. Be prepared to make a difficult decision about whether to show up at a work event
        or spend an evening with a special someone. They might not be as forgiving about being
        second place as they have been in the past, so don\'t assume that they\'re as supportive of
        your ambition as you think they are. When you plan something with someone, you need to stay
        true to your word.
    </string>
    <string name="aquariusText">Your energy isn\'t going to be easily integrated into anyone
        else\'s today, so it\'s not a very good idea to get involved with a lot of different people.
        You are feeling so strong and independent that you don\'t want to compromise, and that could
        rub people the wrong way. But you have a vision that must be obeyed. This is a powerful
        phase for you. You can put your ideas into action and start on those ambitious plans you\'ve
        been formulating for so long.
    </string>
    <string name="piscesText">Take another look at your health and diet today. Things have changed
        more than you realize, and it will be time for either a celebration or a complete overhaul.
        If you have slipped a bit, then you need to face facts and trim the fat, literally!
        Investigate new ideas on how to eat more healthfully and exercise more. But if the change
        has been a healthy one, then let yourself take one day off and celebrate. You\'ve got the
        fundamentals and you\'re on your way!
    </string>

</resources>